<searchresult><query>Denso Corporation</query><document id="0"><title>Intelligent portable phone with dual mode operation for automobile use</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6697638B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A system for operating a cellular phone using Bluetooth with a car kit is described. The Bluetooth protocol is used to communicate between the cellular phone and the car kit. A communication can be established between the cellular phone &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="1"><title>Semiconductor substrate manufacturing method</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6251754B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>The invention provides a number of semiconductor substrate manufacturing methods with which, in manufacturing a semiconductor substrate having a semiconductor layer in an insulated state on a supporting substrate, it is possible to obtain &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="2"><title>Liquid crystal cell and its manufacturing method</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5861932A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A pair of electrode panels are supported by plural spacer walls made of photo-resist resin to form a cell gap between electrode panels. The cell gap is filled with liquid crystal, preferably, antiferroelectric liquid crystal. The spacer &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="3"><title>Silicon carbide semiconductor device</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6573534B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor device, comprising: a semiconductor substrate comprising silicon carbide of a first conductivity type; a silicon carbide epitaxial layer of the first conductivity type; a first semiconductor region formed on the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="4"><title>Non-uniformly-rigid barrier wall spacers used to correct problems caused by &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6337730B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>According to this liquid crystal cell, a vacuum to be established between two electrode substrates as a result of the volume shrinkage of a liquid crystal having a high viscosity at the room temperature can be damped by communicating &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="5"><title>Power MOS transistor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6365932B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A new and improved power MOS transistor having a protective diode with an increased breakdown voltage difference and less sheet resistivity is disclosed. In an up-drain type MOSFET, an n-type well layer has its top surface in which an &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="6"><title>Obstacle warning system for a vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5751211A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>As provided here, an obstacle warning system for a vehicle is capable of issuing an alarm accurately according to the curved state of a road. When the road is curved, the system sets the correction time counter on the basis of the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="7"><title>Information service device having simple data retrieval capabilities</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5948041A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>When a user selects an item from a menu displayed by a display unit of a vehicular terminal, a control unit of the vehicular terminal receives information data and location data corresponding to the information data from an information &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="8"><title>Semiconductor substrate and method of manufacturing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6534380B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Before a semiconductor substrate and a base substrate is directly bonded to one another, in a protective film removing step, a contamination protective film formed on the semiconductor substrate to protect it from contamination during an &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="9"><title>Method for manufacturing a semiconductor substrate</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6191007B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Methods for manufacturing semiconductor substrates in which a semiconductor layer for forming semiconductor device therein is formed on a supporting substrate with an insulating film interposed between, with which in forming the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="10"><title>Silicon carbide semiconductor device</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5976936A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A silicon carbide semiconductor device having a high blocking voltage, low loss, and a low threshold voltage is provided. An n + type silicon carbide semiconductor substrate 1, an n - type silicon carbide semiconductor substrate 2, and a p &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="11"><title>Vehicle seat air-conditioning system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6059018A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An air-conditioning case (2d) of a front air-conditioning unit (2) includes therein a branching duct (2c) for dividing the flow of the air-conditioned air to the seat (3) of occupants, and a cool/warm air switch (10) for switching the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="12"><title>Vehicle information communication system and method capable of communicating &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6285931B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a vehicle diagnosis information communication system, electric power is supplied from a battery to a vehicle control computer mounted on the vehicle during a period of vehicle operation, while the electric power is supplied to a radio &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="13"><title>Vehicle diagnosis system having transponder for OBD III</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6225898B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A vehicle diagnosis system can handle with OBD III as well as OBD II by only adding a transponder to an OBD II system. The vehicle diagnosis system includes an engine ECU for controlling an engine device such as injector and storing a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="14"><title>Obstacle recognition system for automotive vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6018308A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An obstacle recognition system for automotive vehicles is provided which is designed to distinguish preceding vehicles from other objects and uses data thereof in intervehicle distance control, for example. The system includes a radar &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="15"><title>Rotary electric machine having a permanent magnet stator and permanent magnet &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6590312B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A rotary electric machine for a hybrid vehicle includes a rotor connected between a vehicle engine and a torque transmission mechanism at the back of the vehicle engine and a stator. The rotor includes an outer rotor portion having an &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="16"><title>Silicon carbide semiconductor device and method for manufacturing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6455892B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In an accumulation mode MOSFET, a surface channel layer is disposed on a p &#8722; type base region between an n + type source region and an n &#8722; type epi layer. The surface channel layer is composed of an n type channel layer formed on the p &#8722; type &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="17"><title>Alternator for an automotive vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5998903A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>The present invention provides a compact, efficient and noiseless alternator for an automotive vehicle which employs a double-layer coil arrangement in a slot for eliminating coil end interference as well as improving the space factor. An &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="18"><title>System and method for driving electric vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5917248A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A T-S converter is composed of a first rotor which has a first control coil, a second rotor and a stator which has a second control coil. The second rotor has a first magnetic field member (such as permanent magnets) which supplies the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="19"><title>Semiconductor device including eutectic bonding portion and method for &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6555901B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A sensing element is formed on a silicon (Si) substrate and covered with a cap. The cap has a leg portion having a titanium layer and a gold layer formed in that order on the lower surface thereof. The silicon substrate has an Si bonding &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="20"><title>Variable focus lens device having temperature fluctuation compensating feature &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6188526B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A variable focus lens device having a temperature compensation function whose construction is simple and which can be inexpensively manufactured. The device has a lens member including a lens container having a transparent elastic film, a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="21"><title>Method of making update information of map data and differential data of map &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6453233B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A differential update method for vehicular navigation apparatus, which can precisely update map data stored in a storage medium to up-to-date contents. When a provider of CD generates original map data for each year, the provider puts a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="22"><title>Pattern display device and game machine including the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US7204753B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A game machines has a back side display unit composed of reels for displaying back patterns, and a front side display unit composed of transparent EL panels for displaying overlapping patterns overlapping with the back patterns. The back &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="23"><title>Controller for hybrid vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6018694A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A gas-sparing vehicle is achieved by a control system for a hybrid vehicle equipped at least with: a hybrid engine which includes at least a first rotary electric unit for deciding the rpm of the engine and a second rotary electric unit &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="24"><title>Process for producing a semiconductor device having a single thermal oxidizing &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5915180A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor device, which has an oxide laver with the thickness thereof being varied from portion to portion of the inner surface of a trench and can be easily produced, and a process of producing the same. An n + type single crystal &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="25"><title>Differentially corrected position location system and method for mobile &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5926133A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A system for determining the location of portable communication devices such as cellular telephones and the like has multiple small, dedicated multipath calibration transponders at known positions. When a portable communication device &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="26"><title>High pressure fuel injection system for internal combustion engine</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6024064A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a high pressure fuel injection system, fuel is pumped up from a fuel tank by a low pressure pump and further pressurized by a high pressure pump. Pressurized fuel is accumulated in a common rail connected to injectors which inject fuel &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="27"><title>Electroluminescent device and method of producing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6207302B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>First and second insulating layers in an EL device are respectively composed of Al 2 O 3 /TiOx:Ba laminated layers. The Al 2 O 3 /TiOx:Ba laminated layers are formed by alternately laminating Al 2 O 3 layers and TiO 2 layers added with Ba by an ALE &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="28"><title>Seat air conditioner for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6179706B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A seat air conditioner for a vehicle has a seat having a pad and a blower unit for forcibly blowing conditioned air toward the seat. The pad has an introduction passage for introducing blown air toward a surface of the pad, plural &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="29"><title>Respiratory disease monitoring system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6450957B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A respiration monitoring system monitors the state of disorder of the respiratory system of a sleeping patient based on the detection of respiratory body movement without the need of putting sensors directly on the patient's body. The &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="30"><title>Semiconductor chip package</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6072240A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor device which improves heat radiation performance and realizes size reduction and enables heat to be radiated swiftly from both of the principal surfaces of a semiconductor chip even when the semiconductor chip has a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="31"><title>Wireless video telephone with ambient light sensor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6687515B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A communication device such as a portable video telephone capable of transmitting images as well as sound is capable of preventing the transmission of dark and featureless images resulting from the device being used in a dark location.</snippet></document><document id="32"><title>Cooling apparatus for high-temperature medium by boiling and condensing &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6005772A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a cooling apparatus, a radiating part mounted on a refrigerant tank is made by stacking refrigerant tubes and fins alternately. A first header and a second header are provided at the ends of the refrigerant tubes. When the cooling &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="33"><title>Stator winding arrangement of alternator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5965965A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An alternator for a vehicle includes a fan for supplying cooling air along an inner circumference of coil-end groups disposed opposite ends of a stator in an axial direction. Each of the coil-end groups is composed of a plurality inner &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="34"><title>Telephone apparatus adaptable to different communication systems</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6198942B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a system having a response hold function as a standard function such as CDMA system, a telephone apparatus transmits a response hold request to a control center when an End key is operated upon arrival of an incoming telephone call &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="35"><title>Map display device</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6710774B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A map display device, which imparts a perspective feeling to a route guidance line so that it can be easily viewed, when buildings and roads are three-dimensionally displayed. A map display device having a control unit for three- &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="36"><title>Alternator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5955810A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An alternator for a vehicle which maintains or improves the cooling performance and which reduces the fan noise caused by the interference between the cooling winds and the stator windings. An armature coil provided on a stator of the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="37"><title>Personal communication terminal with variable speed scroll display feature</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6509907B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A communication terminal having a display capable of scrolling a text message at variable speeds to thereby enhance message readability. A display of 6 full-size characters&#215;3 lines for displaying a character message is provided on the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="38"><title>Two-dimensional code reading apparatus</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6000614A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A two-dimensional code reading apparatus uses the image of a reference pattern of a known shape in the two-dimensional code to compute areas, shapes and positions of cells in the image of the two-dimensional code and corrects these &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="39"><title>Silicon carbide semiconductor device and process for manufacturing same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6133587A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A n - -type source region 5 is formed on a predetermined region of the surface layer section of the p-type silicon carbide semiconductor layer 3 of a semiconductor substrate 4. A low-resistance p-type silicon carbide region 6 is formed on &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="40"><title>Location specific reminders for wireless mobiles</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6957076B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A system allows users of wireless mobile terminals to set reminders, alerts, or other actions to be triggered based on location or dynamics. Such location information may include, but is not limited to, a specific location description &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="41"><title>Air conditioning apparatus for vehicle with thermoelectric dehumidifier in a &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6213198B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An electric element (Peltier element composite) is disposed in a boundary between an outside air introduction passage and an inside air introduction air passage ( 114 ). The Peltier element composite absorbs heat from the inside air in the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="42"><title>Filter element</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5720790A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A filter element made of nonwoven filter fabric includes a plurality of pleated portions and a flange portion formed integrally with the filter portion. The flange portion is formed by a pair of press-forming dies to have a thin and &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="43"><title>Seat air conditioning unit for vehicle and fan combination of blower units of &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6848742B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A seat air conditioning unit includes a seat defining an air passage therein through which air flows toward a seat surface, and first and second blower units for blowing air in the air passage. The first blower unit is provided in a seat &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="44"><title>Semiconductor device and manufacturing method thereof</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6242787B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor device including a reduced surface field strength type LDMOS transistor which can prevent the breakdown of elements at channel formation portions when a reverse voltage is applied to its drain. A P well and an N well are &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="45"><title>Variable valve timing control system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6330870B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A variable valve timing adjuster with an intermediate lock mechanism learns a lock position and a lock release control. During a lock control, a learning of the lock position from a real camshaft phase is repeated to update the learned &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="46"><title>Combined display panel</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6181301B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A transparent electroluminescent display panel overlaps at least a part of a conventional instrument panel, and forms a combined display panel assembly. Overlapping front and back panel displays are selectively displayed. The front &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="47"><title>Cooling apparatus by boiling and cooling refrigerant</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6227287B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A cooling apparatus for cooling a heating body such as a CPU by boiling and condensing refrigerant has a tank having a heating body mounting portion on which the CPU is mounted; a porous metallic sintered body arranged in the tank; and &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="48"><title>Vehicular navigation system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5905451A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A vehicular navigation system capable of establishing a path to a destination to include a road frequently used by the user. First, the present position of the vehicle is located. A road map containing the present position is displayed on &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="49"><title>Shock-resistive printed circuit board and electronic device including the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6274821B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A printed circuit board has a layer including a resin material, which has a tensile breaking strain of approximately 1% or more at a tensile strain rate of 40%/sec at 25&#176; C., and an Izod impact strength of approximately 1 kgf&#183;cm/cm or &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="50"><title>Map displaying apparatus</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6144920A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A map displaying apparatus comprises a displaying device for displaying a map, a map storing device for storing data of multiple maps showing predetermined areas with different scales, a facility storing device for storing data of &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="51"><title>Alternator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6181043B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a stator of an alternator for a vehicle, a stator winding has a plurality of conductor segments having ends extending in opposite directions and a plurality of ball-shaped connected portion between the conductor segments forming &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="52"><title>Surface mount type package unit and method for manufacturing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5901046A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A package body holding an acceleration sensor circuit therein has signal electrodes and four dummy electrodes insulated from the signal electrode on a mounted surface thereof. The signal electrodes are electrically connected to the sensor &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="53"><title>AC generator for vehicles</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6137201A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An AC generator for a vehicle including a rotor with a fan, a stator disposed around the outer periphery of the rotor, and a frame. The stator includes a laminated core having a plurality of slots, a plurality of electric conductors in &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="54"><title>Coolant cooled type semiconductor device</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6542365B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A coolant cooled type semiconductor device capable of achieving a superior heat radiation capability is provided, while having a simple structure. While a plurality of semiconductor modules are arranged in such a manner that main surface &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="55"><title>Vital signal detecting apparatus</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6608562B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A vital signal detecting apparatus comprises an attachable device to be attached to a finger, a sensor having a light-emitting device and a light-receiving device, and a transmitting circuit for transmitting a signal waveform as a pulse &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="56"><title>Apparatus for determining appropriate series of words carrying information to &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6556970B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An apparatus includes a device for generating plural recognition candidates from a user's utterance including a series of words and a device for screening the candidates to select a few appropriate series of words from the candidates. In &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="57"><title>Method of forming a trench with a rounded bottom in a semiconductor device</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6521538B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a method for manufacturing a semiconductor device, first, a trench is formed on a semiconductor substrate by anisotropic etching, and a reaction product is produced and deposited on the inner wall of the trench during the anisotropic &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="58"><title>Route setting device for setting a destination route from a departure point to &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6295503B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A route setting device, which can provide a route setting device which realize a suitable route setting for each vehicle by using vehicle side data in order to comply with a situation where travel of the vehicle is permitted or prohibited &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="59"><title>Radar system installable in an automotive vehicle for detecting a target object</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6040796A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A modulation signal generating section produces a modulation signal for controlling an oscillation frequency of a voltage-controlled oscillator. The modulation signal generating section comprises a triangular wave oscillator producing a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="60"><title>Fuel injection valve and its manufacturing method</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5944262A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A fuel injection valve, having an injector pipe containing a needle valve therein, an electromagnetic coil for driving the needle valve and a yoke forming a magnetic circuit, intermittently injects fuel fed from the top of the injection &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="61"><title>Stator cooling arrangement of alternator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6011332A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An alternator for a vehicle includes a stator, a rotor and a pair of cooling fans fixed on opposite sides of the rotor. The stator winding is composed of a conductor group disposed in the stator core and a pair of annular coil-end groups &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="62"><title>Capacitive physical-quantity detection apparatus</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6257061B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A capacitive physical-quantity detection apparatus includes a movable electrode ( 2 d ) which is displaced in response to a physical quantity. A fixed electrode ( 3, 4 ) opposed to the movable electrode forms a capacitor in conjunction with &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="63"><title>Alternator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6291918B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>It is an object of this invention to provide a compact high-power alternator for a vehicle. It is another object of this invention to provide a low-noise alternator for a vehicle which outputs an increased power during operation at a low &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="64"><title>Adaptive adjustment of sleep duration to increase standby time in wireless &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6829493B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A system for a wireless mobile station is disclosed. The system enables the mobile station to adaptively adjust sleep durations and wakeups during a low power idle mode between paging channel slots. The adjustment of sleep durations and &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="65"><title>Battery control method for hybrid vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6608482B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A battery control system is provided which charges or discharges a storage battery installed in a hybrid vehicle to bring a state-of-charge of the storage battery into agreement with a target one. The system determines whether the state- &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="66"><title>Two-dimensional code and method of optically reading the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6267296B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A two-dimensional code made up of a matrix of cells formed with dark and light squares arranged in a pattern carrying an optically readable binary-coded data, and a method of reading such a two-dimensional code. The two-dimensional code &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="67"><title>Battery pack voltage detection apparatus</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6803766B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A battery cell voltages are read in parallel to a capacitor for each battery block of a battery pack by the use of analog switches. The stored voltages of the capacitors are A/D-converted sequentially through the analog switches. Thereby, &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="68"><title>Refrigeration-cycle device</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6347528B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A gas-injection type refrigeration-cycle device has heat exchanger where refrigerant extracts waste heat from heating devices. In the refrigeration-cycle device, the mode is changed between where lower-pressure refrigerant extracts heat &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="69"><title>Fuel injection valve and method of manufacturing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5996910A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A fuel injection valve has a single pipe member made of composite magnetic material which can be processed to form ferro-magnetic structures and non-magnetic structures. A magnetic fuel connector, a magnetic valve body, a nonmagnetic &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="70"><title>AC generator stator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6147432A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In an alternator for a vehicle, a stator winding is composed of a plurality of U-shaped conductor segments and an annular member. The conductor segments have connection edges connected to one another to form ring-connected coil-ends, and &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="71"><title>Power source control apparatus for hybrid vehicles</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5789881A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A power source control apparatus for parallel and series hybrid vehicles is provided. The power source control apparatus determines a required torque of a power source consisting of a generator-motor and an internal combustion engine &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="72"><title>AC generator for vehicles</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6124660A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An AC generator for vehicles includes a field rotor, a stator disposed around said field rotor and a frame for supporting the rotor and the stator. The stator has a laminated core having a plurality of slots, aluminum conductors housed in &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="73"><title>Semiconductor physical quantity sensor device having semiconductor sensor chip &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5948991A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An IC chip for signal processing circuit is enclosed in a mold IC and a pressure sensitive element unit is integrally provided thereon. When the mold IC is housed in a case, the mold IC is fixed to the case under a state where ends of &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="74"><title>Vehicle classifying apparatus and a toll system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6195019B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A class of a vehicle (VHC) is judged from distance data obtained by scanning on a lane with at least a laser beam in the longitudinal direction LD of the lane, wherein the scanning line may be inclined. Distance data may be further &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="75"><title>Organic electroluminescent panel</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6447934B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An organic electroluminescent panel having two luminescent layers interposed between a pair of electrode layers emits white light or colored light. One luminescent layer is composed of a hole transport host material and a first &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="76"><title>Semiconductor device having radiation structure</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6703707B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor device includes two semiconductor chips that are interposed between a pair of radiation members, and thermally and electrically connected to the radiation members. One of the radiation members has two protruding portions &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="77"><title>Compressor control device for vehicle air conditioner</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5867996A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A compressor control device is presented to control driving power of a compressor of a vehicle air conditioner. The control device is composed of a first means which detects ambient temperature conditions of the vehicle, a second means &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="78"><title>Fuel injection control system for engine</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6755176B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A fuel injection is carried out as n split injections. Each of injection quantities is defined by dividing an injection quantity into n fuel injections. A FCCB correction and an ISC correction are carried out while n split injection &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="79"><title>Alternator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5936326A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>It is an object of this invention to provide an alternator for a vehicle in which all electric conductors forming bridge portions are sufficiently exposed to cooling winds so that the cooling performance is remarkably improved. It is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="80"><title>Vehicle wheel information supply device and wheel tire abnormality indicating &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6275148B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A vehicle wheel information supply device for supplying wheel information relating to a state of a wheel of a vehicle, including a wheel state detector for detecting the state of the wheel, a wheel information generator for generating the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="81"><title>Navigation device, digital map display system, digital map displaying method in &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6772063B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A navigation device including a registration unit for registering an index designated by a user's operation and data of a spot coordinate in association with each other, and a display for displaying a plurality of registered indexes as a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="82"><title>Semiconductor device with a protective sheet to affix a semiconductor chip</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6255741B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A heat resisting resin sheet is bonded to a semiconductor chip as a protective cap for protecting a beam structure provided on the semiconductor chip, through a heat resisting adhesive. The heat resisting resin sheet is composed of a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="83"><title>Vehicle air conditioning system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6330909B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a vehicle air-conditioning system, an evaporator is disposed in an air-conditioning case to form a bypass passage through which air bypasses the evaporator, and an opening degree of the bypass passage is adjusted by a bypass door. When &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="84"><title>Electric power unit</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6220383B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An electric power unit is composed of a secondary battery, a cooling fan, a fan motor and a case for the secondary battery, the cooling fan and the fan motor. The case has a partition for isolating the fan motor from the secondary battery &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="85"><title>Two-dimensional code, reading and producing method and recording medium storing &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6279830B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A two-dimensional code includes a plurality of cells arranged in a predetermined two-dimensional pattern. The code comprises an information recording region constituted by a plurality of blocks. Each block involves a recording mode &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="86"><title>Rotational power converter for hybrid electric vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6380653B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A rotational power converter is composed of a stator fixed to a cylindrical housing and a first rotor and a second rotor rotatably supported in the housing. The first rotor is driven by an internal combustion engine, and electric power is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="87"><title>Thermoelectric generating device</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US7100369B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A thermoelectric generating device has a thermoelectric element which utilizes an exhaust gas from an engine as a high temperature heat source and an engine coolant as a low temperature heat source in order to generate electricity. An &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="88"><title>AC generator stator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6201332B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In an alternator stator for vehicle, each of the phase-windings includes first and second coil-end groups at opposite axial ends the stator core. Each of the slots includes radially aligned six layers. Each of the phase-windings comprises &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="89"><title>Alternator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6097130A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>It is an object of this invention to provide a compact high-power alternator for a vehicle which is good in cooling performance, efficiency, and cost without decreasing a coil resistance or using a magnet. The alternator for the vehicle &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="90"><title>Semiconductor dynamical quantity sensor device having electrodes in Rahmen &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6151966A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor accelerometer device is formed on an SOI substrate by micro-machining. A movable unit is supported at both ends, and a weight portion is movable in response to acceleration exerted in the detection direction. A movable &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="91"><title>Intersection warning system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5940010A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An intersection warning system provided in a vehicle includes a distance detecting unit detecting a distance between a position at which the vehicle runs toward an intersection and a boundary position (a stop line) set for vehicles to &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="92"><title>Method of reading two-dimensional code and storage medium thereof</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6360948B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A method of reading information out of a two-dimensional code made up of a matrix of cells having a given optical pattern is provided. The two-dimensional code has location symbols used to locate the two-dimensional code and alignment &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="93"><title>Semiconductor physical quantity sensor with stopper portion</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6065341A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A mass portion of a movable portion is supported by an anchor portion protruding from a substrate through a beam portion. A stopper portion fixed to the substrate through another anchor portion is disposed on a side opposite to the mass &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="94"><title>Ejector cycle system with critical refrigerant pressure</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6477857B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In an ejector cycle system using carbon dioxide as refrigerant, an ejector decompresses and expands refrigerant from a radiator to suck gas refrigerant evaporated in an evaporator, and converts an expansion energy to a pressure energy to &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="95"><title>Silicon carbide semiconductor device and process for its production</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5744826A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor substrate 4 consisting of an n + -type substrate 1, an n - -type silicon carbide semiconductor layer 2 and a p-type silicon carbide semiconductor layer 3, made of hexagonal crystal-based single crystal silicon carbide with &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="96"><title>Silicon carbide semiconductor device and method of manufacturing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6165822A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A vertical type power MOSFET made of silicon carbide includes a surface channel layer doped with nitrogen as dopant with a concentration equal to or less than 1&#215;10 15 cm -3 . Accordingly, when a gate oxide film is formed on the surface &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="97"><title>Air conditioning apparatus for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6047770A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In an air conditioning apparatus for a vehicle, a water/refrigerant heat exchanger is disposed at a refrigerant discharge side of a compressor of a refrigerant cycle, and a cooling unit for cooling a heat-generating unit with refrigerant &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="98"><title>Semiconductor physical quantity sensor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5987989A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor physical quantity sensor includes a substrate and a beam structure having movable electrodes and spacing a given distance from an upper surface of the substrate. First fixed electrodes and second fixed electrodes are &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="99"><title>FM-CW radar apparatus for measuring relative speed of and distance to an object</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5731778A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An FM-CW radar which is suitable for automotive anti-collision systems, for example, is provided. This radar outputs a radar signal in the form of a triangular wave whose frequency is increased at a given rate and decreased at a given &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="100"><title>Method of controlling battery condition of self-generation electric vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6232744B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>This invention provides a method of controlling condition of an assembled battery mounted in a self-generation electric vehicle. The method is comprised of the following steps: detecting battery voltage and battery current repeatedly;</snippet></document><document id="101"><title>Semiconductor device</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6054752A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor device comprises a semiconductor substrate including a first conductivity type first semiconductor layer and a second conductivity type second semiconductor layer formed on the first semiconductor layer. A unit cell for &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="102"><title>Semiconductor device and method of manufacturing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6118152A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A silicon layer provided in a silicon substrate through a buried oxide film includes a silicon island partitioned by a trench. A surface of the silicon island in the trench is covered with a side wall oxide film, and LDMOS transistors are &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="103"><title>Fuel supply system having a suction filter in a sub-tank</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5769061A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A fuel pump for pumping fuel is provided in a sub-tank suspended in a fuel tank in order to reserve a fuel volume necessary for the fuel pump to be started on an inlet side of the fuel pump in the fuel tank. A fuel level holding member &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="104"><title>Semiconductor physical quantity sensor and production method thereof</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6240782B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor physical quantity sensor includes a substrate, a beam-structure movable portion and a fixed portion. The beam-structure movable portion is suspended by four anchors formed of polycrystalline films. A rectangular mass is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="105"><title>Exhaust emission purification apparatus for an internal combustion engine</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5842341A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An exhaust emission gas purification apparatus for an internal combustion engine is disclosed, in which a proper purification rate can be maintained even at a transient time by suppressing an excessive temperature increase of a lean NO x &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="106"><title>Casing for electronic control devices</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6407925B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A casing for an electronic control device, by which a cover and a casing body are reliably sealed up while preventing the cover from warping or from being distorted, although the cover is made of a thin sheet material. The electronic &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="107"><title>Method for manufacturing semiconductor substrate having an epitaxial film in &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6495294B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A trench is formed in a silicon substrate, and an epitaxial film is formed on the substrate and in the trench. After a part of the epitaxial film formed around an opening portion of the trench is etched, another epitaxial film is formed &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="108"><title>Automatic lighting device and method for controlling light</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US7639149B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An automatic lighting device includes an illuminance detector for detecting an external illuminance around a vehicle, a light controller for turning on/off a vehicular light, a driver's characteristics detector for acquiring information &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="109"><title>Hybrid type compressor driven by engine and electric motor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6234769B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a hybrid type compressor, a one-way clutch is provided between a magnet rotor and a rotor shaft for allowing rotational driving force generated by an electric motor unit to be transmitted only from a rotor to a shaft. Thus, the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="110"><title>Total-focus imaging apparatus using a variable-focus lens</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6344930B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A total-focus imaging apparatus comprises a variable-focus lens unit with a focal position thereof changeable at high speeds, a CCD element, a microcomputer and a liquid-crystal display unit. The microcomputer includes an image memory, an &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="111"><title>Battery cooling system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6106972A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A cooling apparatus communicates through a communicating pipe with an inside space of an airtight casing in which a plurality of battery cells are hermetically held. The cooling apparatus and the inside space of the airtight casing are &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="112"><title>Control apparatus for robot having an arm moving within allowable working area</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6166504A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A robot that stops an arm within a limitation position of a predetermined working area when the arm is going to exceed the predetermined working area. ACPU of controller calculates a position and a speed of an arm at a next sampling time &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="113"><title>Vehicle air conditioner</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6311763B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a vehicle air conditioner, a first air passage through which outside air flows and a second air passage through which inside air flows are provided to be partitioned from each other, so that outside air in the first air passage is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="114"><title>Air-conditioning device for hybrid vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6073456A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An air-conditioning device includes a control system for saving fuel consumed to drive the device and for enhancing comfortability of passengers at the same time. The air-conditioning device is operated under a cooling mode emphasizing &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="115"><title>Method and apparatus for manufacturing AC-generator's stator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6249956B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>The object of the present invention is to provide a method and an apparatus for manufacturing a stator to improve accuracy in inserting conductor segments ( 3, 31, 32 ) into slots ( 2 ). The apparatus according to the present invention &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="116"><title>Rotary electric machine having resin covered joined portions</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6333573B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A rotary electric machine has a stator winding which forms a coil end group on an axial end of a stator. A plurality of conductors are regularly arranged in a row in the coil end group, and an insulating resin is soaked into there between &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="117"><title>Inverter-integrated motor for an automotive vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US7207187B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A bus-bar integrated plate and outer frame section, arranged into a double-deck structure and having numerous bus bars molded with a resin molding plate portion, is provided as a wiring for connecting power switching elements and a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="118"><title>Seat air conditioning unit for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6685553B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A seat air conditioning unit includes a seat defining an air passage in a seat member and a blower unit for blowing air into the air passage. The air passage includes an air introduction passage communicating with the blower unit, air &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="119"><title>Semiconductor mechanical sensor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6550331B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor mechanical sensor having a new structure in which a S/N ratio is improved. In the central portion of a silicon substrate 1, a recess portion 2 is formed which includes a beam structure. A weight is formed at the tip of the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="120"><title>Air conditioning apparatus for vehicle seat</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6105667A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An air conditioning apparatus for a vehicle seat includes a seat blower unit disposed in a lower side of the seat, and a seat duct for leading air from an air conditioning unit to the seat through the seat blower unit. In the air &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="121"><title>Laminate-type battery and process for its manufacture</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6335114B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>There are provided coiled electrode batteries with high yields, while short-circuiting in the batteries is prevented. A coiled electrode battery according to the invention has coiled electrodes consisting of positive and negative poles 21 &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="122"><title>Vehicle power supply system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US7336002B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A main power source is, for example, an ordinary Pb battery. At the time of starting an engine, the main power source supplies power to a starter. The main power source is given a higher priority than an auxiliary power source to supply &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="123"><title>Synchronous electric machine having auxiliary permanent magnet</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5955807A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A synchronous electric machine includes a stator having an armature winding, a rotor having axially laminated magnetic sheets and a field coil, a plurality of permanent magnets disposed in the rotor to form N-pole and S-pole on the outer &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="124"><title>Method of manufacturing silicon carbide semiconductor device with high &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6221700B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A surface portion of a p type base region is made amorphous as an amorphous layer by implanting nitrogen ions which serve as impurities and ions which do not serve as impurities. After that, the amorphous layer is crystallized to have a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="125"><title>Composite clay material and method for producing the same, blend material and &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6103817A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A composite clay material with the interlayer distance sufficiently expanded by dispersing clay mineral in a low polar polymer on a molecular level and the method for producing the same, blend material and composite clay rubber material &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="126"><title>Toll collection system of toll road and in-vehicle unit for the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6042008A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>To ensure the toll collection of a vehicle carrying an in-vehicle unit without stopping the vehicle at an entrance toll gate or an exit toll gate, an entrance toll gate lane is equipped sequentially from the entrance with a vehicle class &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="127"><title>Voltage balancer device for combination battery</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6081095A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A large number of rechargeable unit cells connected in series forming a combination battery are divided into groups of cells, each group including several cells, preferably, three to five cells. Voltage unevenness among the cells in each &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="128"><title>Infant condition monitoring system and method using load cell sensor sheet</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6280392B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An infant condition monitoring system has a sensor sheet including uniformly arranged plural pressure sensitive load cells. An ECU in an electronic unit connected to the sensor sheet calculates an infant's breathing signal, sleeping &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="129"><title>Seat air conditioner having mechanism following passenger seat</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6478369B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A seat air duct includes a floor duct fixed to the floor surface of vehicle cabin and flexible ducts. The upper wall of the floor duct is partially formed by flexible slide walls. The flexible slide walls are formed in an accordion and &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="130"><title>Automatic deceleration control system, vehicle-to-obstacle distance control &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6070682A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Automatic acceleration/deceleration control for an automotive vehicle is provided which may be used in an automatic deceleration system and a vehicle-to-obstacle distance control system. The automatic acceleration/deceleration control &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="131"><title>Vehicle display system with drive enforcement control</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6256558B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A vehicle display system which keeps a driver from inputting data into the system while driving a vehicle, but which permits a person in the front passenger seat to perform the data input operations. A main ECU inhibits data input &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="132"><title>Air conditioning apparatus for seat of vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5921100A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An air conditioning apparatus for a seat of a vehicle includes a seat air-blowing unit disposed in a lower portion of the seat, and a seat duct for blowing air from an air conditioning unit to the seat air-blowing unit. The air &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="133"><title>System for restarting internal combustion engine when engine restart request &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US8036815B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a system, a starter includes a motor for rotatably driving an output shaft with a pinion and an actuator that shifts the pinion toward a ring gear to be engaged with the ring gear. A monitor unit monitors a rotational speed of the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="134"><title>Rotary electric machine and method of manufacturing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6140735A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a multi-phase rotary electric machine, each of phase windings is composed of a pair of semi-phase-windings having a starting end portion, a plurality of series-connected wave-coil units, and a connecting end. Each of the wave-coil &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="135"><title>Method of manufacturing silicon carbide semiconductor device using active and &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6297100B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a vertical MOSFET, an inactive ion species is ion-implanted into a J-FET portion, a surface channel layer, and/or a base region. The inactive ion species fill intrinsic carbon vacancies or interact with interstitial Si atoms, which are &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="136"><title>Mounting structure of semiconductor element</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6376906B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a mounting structure of a flip chip IC, the flip chip IC is mounted on an alumina laminated substrate through conductive lands of the substrate and bumps of the flip chip IC. A space between the flip chip IC and the substrate is filled &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="137"><title>Air bag apparatus with movably mounted door</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5887891A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In an air bag apparatus which is installed at an opening of a dashboard, a case fixed to a vehicle dashboard has an opening and side walls having through holes. A door to cover the opening of the case has connecting portions having &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="138"><title>Rotary electric machine for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6417592B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a vehicle rotary electric machine, a stator core has a plurality of slots accommodating a plurality of conductors forming a plurality of phase windings. The phase winding includes a plurality of parallel-connected winding sections.</snippet></document><document id="139"><title>Meter for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6302551B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A meter for a vehicle has a scale plate, a pointer and a plurality of light sources. A first light source lights a scale plate up from a backside thereof. A second light source lights the scale plate up through a light guiding plate. A &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="140"><title>Dry etching method for semiconductor substrate</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6090718A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>After performing an etching process with respect to one substrate, the substrate is taken out from an etching chamber. Then, a dummy substrate is disposed in the etching chamber and a cleaning process is performed. The cleaning process &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="141"><title>Rotary electric machine having auxiliary permanent magnets</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5973435A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A rotor of an alternator having a plurality of claw poles, a plurality of auxiliary permanent magnets and a magnet holder for the permanent magnets. The magnet holder is composed of soft resinous holding members, connecting bands and heat &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="142"><title>Rotor for a rotating electric machine</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5925964A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>The present invention prevents the degradation of the power generating efficiency of an alternating current generator by preventing the expansion of an air gap formed between pole cores and a stator core, achieves low-noise operation by &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="143"><title>Rotation angle detector having first molded member integrating magnetic sensing &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6407543B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Non-contact type Hall ICs detecting an rotation angle of a throttle valve, a stator core strengthening a magnetic field around the Hall ICs, a lead frame connecting the Hall ICs to an outside ECU are integrated in a sensor cover by resin &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="144"><title>Alternator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5986375A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An alternator for a vehicle includes a stator having a stator core, a stator winding having a first coil-end group and a second coil-end group on the opposite ends of the stator core The alternator further includes a rectifier disposed &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="145"><title>Exhaust cleaning device of internal combustion engine</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US7111455B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An exhaust cleaning device of an internal combustion engine includes a particulate filter disposed in an exhaust duct of the internal combustion engine. A regeneration control increases the temperature of the particulate filter to &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="146"><title>Semiconductor device with flat protective adhesive sheet and method of &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6245593B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor device has a semiconductor wafer having sensing portions exposed on a surface thereof and an adhesive sheet attached to the semiconductor wafer as a protective cap to cover the sensing portions. The adhesive sheet is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="147"><title>Portable terminal device with power saving backlight control</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6725064B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A cellular phone has back light illumination for its display unit and a key unit, and is capable of receiving internet information, receiving karaoke songs, or receiving and sending electronic mails. In the case that the cellular phone is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="148"><title>FM-CW radar system for measuring distance to and relative speed of a target</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6317073B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An FM-CW radar is provided which may be employed in anti-collision systems or cruise control systems installed in moving objects such as automotive vehicles. The radar produces a first spectrum using a portion of a beat signal in a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="149"><title>Electroluminescent display with constant current control circuits in scan &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6121943A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>To reduce the influence of generation of heat at scan driver ICs during the application of a scan signal with reduced time of charge and discharge and to eliminate the problem of a rush current, in an EL display where scan driver Ics &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="150"><title>FMCW radar system for detecting distance, relative velocity and azimuth of a &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5751240A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Beat signals of respective receiver channels CH1 and CH2, produced by mixing their receiving signals with a transmission signal, are subjected to Fourier transformation to detect the frequency and phase of peak frequency components in &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="151"><title>Control system for engine</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6571765B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>The engine control system has an ECU that supplies relatively large amount of EGR gas and delays an injection timing in order to decrease temperature in a combustion chamber. When an engine is operated under a warming up operation or a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="152"><title>Vehicle travel-route guidance apparatus with internal intersection discount &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6134501A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A vehicle travel-route guidance apparatus. The apparatus includes a map-storing device having internal intersection information that is furnished for executing a right-hand turn or a left-hand turn to bypass an intersection. The guidance &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="153"><title>Encrypting communications between wireless mobile units</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6792112B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A wireless mobile unit includes a voice encoder circuit that receives an analog voice signal and creates digital voice data representing a user's voice. The mobile unit receives an encryption key entered by the user, typically on the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="154"><title>Route guidance apparatus</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6151552A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A route guidance apparatus comprises a guiding device for, every time a turning point for which guidance is to be provided existing on a route for reaching a destination is approached, providing travel guidance for that turning point by &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="155"><title>AC generator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5994802A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A stator winding is composed of a first and second of three-phase windings. Each of them has three separate Y-connected or &#916;-connected coils which are wound on the teeth of the stator core at a 2 &#960;/3 short pitch. The second three-phase &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="156"><title>Variable valve timing control apparatus and method for engines</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6505586B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A variable valve timing control apparatus is constructed so as to supply hydraulic pressure to an unlocking chamber for unlocking a lock pin only from a retarding chamber. In cranking an engine, a hydraulic pressure control valve is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="157"><title>Stator of AC generator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6147430A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a stator of an ac generator for vehicle, a plurality of insulators are disposed in the slots of the stator to insulate the stator winding from the stator core. Each of the insulators has a smooth edge at one end and a stopper portion &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="158"><title>Stator of vehicle AC generator and method of manufacturing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6208060B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A stator of an ac generator for vehicle has a stator core which is a lamination of steel sheets and has a plurality of slots cut out in a cutout direction. A plurality of insulators and, subsequently, electric conductors are respectively &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="159"><title>Exhaust gas recirculation system having cooler</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6826903B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An exhaust gas recirculation (EGR) system of an internal combustion engine has an EGR cooler in an EGR passage connecting an exhaust manifold with an intake manifold. The EGR cooler cools EGR gas recirculated through the EGR passage.</snippet></document><document id="160"><title>Angular velocity sensor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6119518A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An angular velocity sensor includes a tuning-fork oscillator having a pair of arms jointed by a trunk, the pair of arms extending in parallel to each other, first and second driving piezoelectric elements arranged only on one surface of &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="161"><title>Cooling apparatus boiling and condensing refrigerant</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5998863A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>According to the present invention, the cooling apparatus includes a refrigerant tank to which a semiconductor device is attached, a connection chamber which is open to the central portion of the refrigerant tank on the side opposite to &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="162"><title>Diagnostic method and apparatus for vehicle having communication disabling &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6067009A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a diagnostic method and apparatus for a vehicle, a transponder for performing a communication with an external receiver and an engine ECU are connected on a communication line. During a first inappropriate period in which noises are &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="163"><title>Obstacle detecting system for automotive vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6147637A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An automotive obstacle detecting system is provided which includes a radar to measure the distance to a target present within a detectable zone. The system monitors a distance limit measurable by the radar and determines a reduction in &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="164"><title>Method and apparatus for driving and controlling on-vehicle loads</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US7173347B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In an apparatus for driving and controlling plural on-vehicle electrical loads, an on-vehicle power supply generates power to be supplied the loads each having a priority. A power calculating device calculates a current available amount &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="165"><title>Vehicle seat air conditioning system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6871696B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A vehicle seat air-conditioning system is used with a main air-conditioning unit which operates in one of a plurality of air blow modes. The main air-conditioning unit has an air-conditioned air outlet-port for supplying air-conditioned &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="166"><title>Semiconductor physical quantity sensor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6494096B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor acceleration sensor, which prevents an adhesion of a movable electrode to a first or second fixed electrode due to an electrostatic attracting force generated therebetween. The sensor has a weight portion and movable &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="167"><title>Semiconductor apparatus having high withstand voltage</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6150697A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An island region surrounded by a trench is provided in an SOI substrate. The island region is further surrounded by a buffer region with a buffer region contact layer. In the island region, a source region is annularly provided around a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="168"><title>Silicon carbide semiconductor device and method of fabricating the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6551865B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Openings are formed in a laminate of a polycrystalline silicon film and an LTO film on a channel layer. While the laminate is used as a mask, impurities are implanted into a place in the channel layer which is assigned to a source region.</snippet></document><document id="169"><title>Semiconductor switching element driving circuit</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6717785B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor switching element driving circuit comprises an overcurrent limiting circuit which instantaneously drops a voltage of a gate terminal of an IGBT when a main IGBT current becomes larger than a predetermined level i1. An &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="170"><title>Semiconductor device having a vertical type semiconductor element</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6982459B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A vertical type MOS field effect transistor has a super junction structure between a source electrode and an N + -type drain region. The super junction structure is constituted by a plurality of P-type single crystal silicon regions and a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="171"><title>Engine exhaust purification system and method having NOx occluding and reducing &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6244046B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A NOx catalyst is attached to an engine exhaust pipe, an A/F sensor is disposed upstream of the NOx catalyst, and an O 2 sensor is disposed downstream of the NOx catalyst. A CPU in an ECU executes a lean combustion control so that NOx in &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="172"><title>Antenna for portable radio communication device and method of transmitting &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6597320B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An antenna for a portable radio communication device is constructed with a conductive shield plate provided in a casing made of resin and shaped to be worn on a human body. The shield plate is capacitively coupled with a part of the human &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="173"><title>Centrifugal blower</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5839879A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A scroll casing of a centrifugal blower holds a centrifugal fan therein and defines an air passage around the centrifugal fan. The scroll casing has a scroll starting position at the most upstream portion of the air passage, a scroll &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="174"><title>Heating heat exchanger with electric heat emitter</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5995711A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A heat-exchanging core portion includes a plurality of tubes arranged in parallel and a plurality of fin members disposed between a pair of adjacent tubes. While an electric heat emitting unit is constructed by supporting a heat emitting &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="175"><title>Electric rotary machine having a plurality of conductor segments and method of &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6459177B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>The invention provides a rotary electric machine and method of manufacturing same, having a plurality of conductor segments inserted in a plurality of slots of a stator core. The conductor segments are welded together at adjacent &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="176"><title>Fluid injection valve</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5931391A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A fluid injection valve includes a valve seat having a conical concave surface and a valve seat surface, a needle having an edge surface and an annular contact surface whose diameter is Ds, an orifice plate having a perforated surface &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="177"><title>Fuel vapor treatment system for internal combustion engine</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6971375B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A pump generates a gas flow within a measurement passage having an orifice. A differential pressure sensor detects a pressure difference between both ends of the orifice. Switching valves are disposed in the measurement passage to create &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="178"><title>Vehicle AC generators stator and method of manufacturing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6242836B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a stator of a vehicle ac generator, a slot insulator has a portion closing the opening of a slot. Therefore, portions of the stator winding disposed in the slot can be retained in the slot without an additional member, and water or the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="179"><title>Centrifugal type blower unit</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6299409B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a centrifugal type blower unit, a diameter of an air suction port is set to be larger than a minimum inner diameter of a centrifugal fan, and a slanting portion is formed in each blade of the centrifugal fan at a side of the air &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="180"><title>Exhaust gas filtering system having particulate filter for internal combustion &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6969413B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A flow rate of gas supplied to a diesel particulate filter is increased when it is determined that rapid combustion of collected particulates, which are collected by the particulate filter, is likely to occur based on an operating state &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="181"><title>Mounting structure including communication system for transmitting multiplex &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6756697B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A mounting structure for mounting accessories on a designed interior member in a vehicle compartment includes a plurality of mounting portions. Each of the mounting portions includes a non-contact type power sending terminal and a vehicle &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="182"><title>Vehicle navigation system and method for setting direction labels for &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6119066A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>When a vehicle is within a predetermined distance from an intersection during the execution of navigation operations, a navigation system displays an enlarged guide map of the same intersection. The guide map shows direction labels that &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="183"><title>Automotive anti-collision and alarm system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5818355A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An estimated travelling curve La (radius Rea) of a system vehicle is obtained based on a first group of sampling data (X1, Y1) through (X5, Y5). Alarm area WA1a is set as a region surrounded by a pair of circular arcs parallel shifted &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="184"><title>Exhaust gas cleaning system having particulate filter</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6758039B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In an exhaust gas cleaning system of an internal combustion engine having a diesel particulate filter (DPF), measuring accuracy of a collection quantity of particulate matters collected by the DPF is estimated based on an accelerator &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="185"><title>Obstacle recognition system for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5798727A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In an obstacle recognition system for a vehicle, transmission wave is irradiated per given angle for recognizing an obstacle ahead of the subject vehicle based on angle/distance data obtained from received reflected wave. A position of &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="186"><title>Multi-rotor synchronous machine permitting relative movement between rotors</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6998757B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A compact and reliable structure of a multi-rotor synchronous machine which may be employed as a generator/motor for automotive vehicles is provided. The machine includes an outer rotor having permanent magnets, an inner rotor having &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="187"><title>Vehicular relay device, in-vehicle communication system, failure diagnostic &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6694235B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A gateway ECU identifies a requested ECU from a plurality of ECUs through a LAN based on an access request of an external device for requesting access to the requested ECU and determines whether the external device has been authorized to &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="188"><title>Vehicle present position detection apparatus, vehicle present position display &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6226591B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Navigation system, which can improve an accuracy of a travel distance calculation and an accuracy of present position detection even if an accuracy of a pulse data from a vehicle speed sensor is relatively low. The navigation system &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="189"><title>System and method capable of automatically switching information output format</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6243675B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In an information processing system such as a navigation system or a portable information terminal unit, information output mode of a display unit to a user is switchable to a plurality of output modes. The navigation system switches the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="190"><title>Stator arrangement of vehicle AC generator</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6204586B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A stator of a vehicle AC generator includes a stator core having a plurality of slots and a plurality of phase-windings formed of a plurality of conductor members inserted in said plurality of slots. The stator winding has first and &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="191"><title>Accessory device driving apparatus for vehicles</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6501190B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An accessory device driving apparatus is disposed between an internal combustion engine and an accessory device of a vehicle. The driving apparatus is constructed as a coaxial dual rotor-type electric motor/generator that has two &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="192"><title>Engine-motor hybrid vehicle control apparatus and method having engine &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6269290B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In an engine-motor hybrid vehicle, vehicle drive regions are divided into a plurality of groups specified by a plurality of operation state variables. A learning variable set for each drive region is updated according to an amount of a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="193"><title>Spark plug having a noble metallic firing tip bonded to an electric discharge &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6215235B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A spark plug for an internal combustion engine comprises a noble metallic firing tip laser welded on the opposing surface of either a central electrode or a grounded electrode. A fused junction layer, formed between the noble metallic &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="194"><title>Navigation system having in-vehicle and portable modes</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6816783B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A navigation system executes a portable mode for guiding a person when a GPS antenna is connected with it and a speed signal has not been inputted for ten seconds or more. The portable mode enables a predetermined function being &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="195"><title>Exhaust gas filter regenerating apparatus effectively burning particulate &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6854265B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Particulate material collected in a filter (PM) is burnt through a selected one of partial and perfect regenerating processes. The partial regenerating process starts, when an amount of PM is predicted to exceed a value between 2 to 10 g/ &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="196"><title>Motor vehicle dehumidifier with drying agent and drying agent regenerative &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6205805B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A motor vehicle dehumidifier, including a dehumidifying drying agent, that can provide a required dehumidifying capacity with a reduced overall quantity of drying agent compared to conventional drying agent-based dehumidifiers. In the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="197"><title>Battery temperature control device for controlling the temperature of a battery &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6750630B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Air for cooling a battery is supplied to the battery from a rear unit through a duct. In this way, the temperature of the air blown to the battery can be reduced in comparison to a case where inside air is taken from a passenger &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="198"><title>Refrigerant evaporator with refrigerant distribution</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6449979B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An evaporator has plural tubes arranged in parallel with each other in a width direction perpendicular to an air flowing direction. The tubes are further arranged in two rows in the air flowing direction, and tank portions extending in &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="199"><title>Vehicle seat air conditioning system having electric heater and blower unit</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6722148B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=1&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Electric heaters and blower units are disposed inside an occupant seat having exterior cover members, each of which has a plurality of outlet openings. Each electric heater heats the corresponding exterior cover member, and each blower &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="200"><title>Stator arrangement of alternator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5982068A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a stator of an alternator for a vehicle including a stator core and a multi-phase stator winding, the stator winding is composed of a plurality of conductor segments having a pair of conductor members connected with one another to form &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="201"><title>Structure of radar system with multi-receiver channel</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6292129B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A radar apparatus is provided which includes a transmitter, a receiver, and a signal processor. The transmitter produces a transmit signal which is so modulated in frequency as to change with time cyclically and transmits the transmit &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="202"><title>Information service system for providing terminal users with terminal user &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US7065525B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An information service system having user terminals and a center in which information according to a request for retrieval is provided to users at a low cost while simplifying setting of conditions for retrieval at the user terminals is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="203"><title>Automotive air-conditioner with vent and air-mixing door interlocking mechanism</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6138749A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A motor vehicle air-conditioner having a structure that reduces production costs. Main and sub air-mixing doors and an inner-air FOOT door are mechanically interlocked with a single air-mixing door actuator. The shape of an engagement &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="204"><title>Cooling device boiling and condensing refrigerant</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6360814B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A cooling device for cooling a heat-generating member includes a refrigerant tank for boiling liquid refrigerant by heat from the heat-generating member and a radiator for cooling and condensing gas refrigerant from the refrigerant tank.</snippet></document><document id="205"><title>Control apparatus for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6064931A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A wheel load of each wheel or a vehicle body load is estimated based on a gain of a resonance frequency of a tire, and the estimated wheel load or vehicle body load is applied to a braking control or an acceleration control. Further, a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="206"><title>Rotation transmitter having torque limiting mechanism</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6332842B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A torque limiting mechanism includes an axial space formed in a cylindrical wall of a pulley, and a pin protruding and extending from a back surface of a discharge disc. The pin is inserted into the axial space, and a rubber damper is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="207"><title>Structure of robot control system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6091219A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A robot control system is provided which controls a plurality of servomotors for moving a hand and articulated arms of a robot. The robot control system includes a plurality of position detectors, a motor control driver, and a serial &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="208"><title>Integrated vehicle control system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US7047117B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An integrated vehicle control system includes various functionalized networks, such as power train group, vehicle motion group, and power source group, each including a plurality of ECUs connected via an individual communication line. A &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="209"><title>Piezoelectric element and injector using the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6845920B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A piezoelectric element and an injector using the same piezoelectric element are disclosed, which are so high in reliability as not to be shorted even in a high humidity environment, are small in size, are low in cost and are high in heat &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="210"><title>Information display apparatus and navigation apparatus</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6762772B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A navigation apparatus, which can reduce time to restore a display condition as much as possible, even when it becomes necessary to restart during executing software, by omitting several initializing processes when the apparatus restarts.</snippet></document><document id="211"><title>Stator of vehicle AC generator and method of manufacturing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6335583B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A stator of an ac generator for vehicle has a stator core which is a lamination of steel sheets and has a plurality of slots cut out in a slot-cutout direction. A plurality of insulators and, subsequently, electric conductors are &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="212"><title>Angular shift determining apparatus for determining angular shift of central &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6025797A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An angular shift determining apparatus is provided which may be employed in an automotive obstacle detection system designed to determine a distance to and angular direction of a target tracked by a radar. The angular shift determining &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="213"><title>Vehicular power supply apparatus and engine-drive-regulation supporting &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6624529B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A power feed portion includes a power storage portion and a power generating portion. The power storage portion includes a storage battery. The power feed portion feeds electric power to a plurality of on-vehicle loads. In cases where the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="214"><title>Method of fabricating electronic circuit device</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6100108A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An electronic circuit device fabrication method securing a bond width of a seal portion when heat treatment is needed in sealing a device cavity by a cap. An electronic part mounting step is executed to secure electronic parts, including &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="215"><title>Fastening means for contacting DC-output terminal with cooling fin in AC &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5977669A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A three-wave rectifying unit of an AC generator has a plus-side cooling fin, a minus-side cooling fin and a DC-output terminal. The DC-output terminal is made of a metal plate which is harder than the plus-side cooling fin to provide &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="216"><title>Automatic engine stop and start system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6754579B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An engine automatic stop and start system monitors a booster negative pressure and a braking operation. A combination of the booster negative pressure and the brake operation can effectively indicate that a booster negative pressure will &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="217"><title>Photoelectric sensor circuit comprising an auxiliary photodiode and a current &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5936231A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>When a third transistor receives first photoelectric currents outputted from a sensing photodiode, the third transistor provides second photoelectric currents to bases of a first transistor and a second transistor, then the first &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="218"><title>Alternator for vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6091169A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>It is an object of this invention to provide a compact high-power alternator for a vehicle. An alternator (1) for a vehicle includes a stator (2) and a rotor (3). The stator (2) serves as an armature. The rotor (3) operates to generate &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="219"><title>Acceleration sensor and process for the production thereof</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6171881B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A single crystal silicon substrate ( 1 ) is bonded through an SiO 2 film ( 9 ) to a single crystal silicon substrate ( 8 ), and the single crystal silicon substrate ( 1 ) is made into a thin film. A cantilever ( 13 ) is formed on the single crystal &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="220"><title>Air bag system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6206409B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An air bag system comprises an air bag having an opening through which gas is supplied. The air bag is folded in a predetermined polygonal shape and is then contained in a pad. An expansion restraining member is provided in the air bag &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="221"><title>Vehicle AC generator and method of manufacturing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6177747B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a stator of a vehicle AC generator, each of stator slots has a circumferential parallel walls and a radial wall opposite a slot-opening. A stator winding has a plurality of radially aligned in-slot portions fitted in each of the slots &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="222"><title>Rotary electric machine</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5994813A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A stator winding has a plurality of conductor members forming coil ends, and each of the conductor members of the coil ends is hardened and heat treated to have hardness which changes along the length of conductor members. Therefore, the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="223"><title>Catalyst activation control system for engines</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6513319B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An engine has variable timing mechanisms, which are controlled in starting an engine to set valve opening overlap of an intake valve and an exhaust valve around 30&#176; CA. In this case, internal EGR is actively conducted and fuel burning &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="224"><title>Hydraulic circuit having a rotary type pump and brake apparatus for a vehicle &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6142581A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A hydraulic circuit has a rotary type pump comprising a rotor rotating with a driving shaft and a casing which holds the rotor and the driving shaft. The casing further comprises an inlet port through which fluid is introduced to spaces &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="225"><title>Motor drive-control device</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6530426B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A motor drive-control device drive-controls a plurality of auxiliary devices with a single motor while securing a necessary capacity of the auxiliary devices side in correspondence with usage conditions. As such, in an air-conditioning &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="226"><title>Centrifugal blower having a bell-mouth ring for reducing noise</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5813831A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A bell-mouth ring is formed with a casing to be disposed proximately at an outer radial side of a shroud. The bell-mouth ring has a deflection wall surface for deflecting a flow of air blown out radially outwardly from the centrifugal &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="227"><title>Air-conditioning unit for vehicle seat</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6736452B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In an air-conditioning unit mounted in a vehicle seat, a resilient member is provided adjacent to a rear surface of a cover member that makes contact with a user. A cushion member is provided between the cover member and the resilient &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="228"><title>Stereoscopic image display device</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6448952B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A device for displaying a stereoscopic image in which cross-talk is suppressed. A left eye image and a right eye image alternately displayed on a liquid crystal display panel are viewed through an eye shutter having a left eye and a right &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="229"><title>Rapid acquisition and system selection of mobile wireless devices using a &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6748217B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>The present invention enhances service system selection by a mobile unit in a wireless communication system. The mobile unit determines its geographic position, and based on that position selects the proper service system. The geographic &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="230"><title>Refrigerant evaporator and manufacturing method for the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6272881B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An evaporator has plural tubes arranged in parallel with each other in a width direction perpendicular to an air flowing direction. The tubes are further arranged in a plural rows in the air flowing direction, and tank portions extending &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="231"><title>Acceleration sensor with ring-shaped movable electrode</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6199430B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An acceleration sensor has a ring-shaped movable electrode connected to an anchor part via beams and a fixed electrode facing the ring-shaped movable electrode defining a specific interval, which are disposed on a substrate. The movable &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="232"><title>Capacitive type physical quantity detecting sensor for detecting physical &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6668614B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A control signal generator transmits a first signal to a movable electrode and a fixed electrode to detect a change in a capacitance formed between the movable electrode and the fixed electrode during a normal physical quantity detection &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="233"><title>Air conditioner</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6035653A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An air conditioner capable of enhancing responsivity of a blowout temperature of conditioned air while preventing occurrence of an overshoot or undershoot condition of the blowout temperature when a user gives an instruction to change the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="234"><title>Fail-safe system in integrated control of vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6463373B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A fail-safe system used in integrated control of a vehicle includes structural-element control portions. Preset priority degrees are given to the structural-element control portions, respectively. A manager control portion stores one or &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="235"><title>Spark plug having iridium containing noble metal chip attached via a molten &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6078129A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a spark plug for an internal combustion engine, a noble metal chip such as an iridium alloy chip is bonded on the tip of a center electrode made of a material such as nickel by laser beam welding. The noble metal chip contains another &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="236"><title>Motor vehicle air-conditioning apparatus with engine speed control</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5924296A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An automobile air-conditioning apparatus in which the compressor torque of a variable capacity refrigerant compressor is estimated with improved accuracy. The compressor torque is measured on the basis of (1) high-side pressure of the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="237"><title>Transmit power control circuit</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6498925B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A transmit power control circuit, which can control a transmit power of a transmit power control circuit through wide dynamic range and can reduce an insertion loss. A first attenuator inputs a radio-frequency signal and outputs an output &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="238"><title>Ceramic honeycomb structure and method of production thereof</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5952079A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>The present invention discloses a ceramic honeycomb structure comprising partition walls 3 that form mutually adjacent flow paths having a polygonal cross-section, and a peripheral wall 5 provided around the circumference of partition &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="239"><title>Rotary electric machine for electric vehicle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6563246B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A rotary electric machine includes a stator core having a plurality of slots disposed at an inner periphery, an armature winding disposed in the slots and a rotor disposed inside the inner periphery of the stator. The rotor includes a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="240"><title>Bump bonding and sealing a semiconductor device with solder</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6313529B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>On a circuit chip on which a processing circuit for sensor outputs is formed, bump electrodes and a sealing bump, which has a shape of rectangular frame and is arranged to surround the bump electrodes, are formed by Sn&#8212;Pb solder. On a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="241"><title>Display device having combined display-panel unit</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6621471B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A display device is comprised of a main display panel, a transparent display panel that is disposed to cover the first display panel, and a control unit. The main display panel indicates a first information pattern, the transparent &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="242"><title>Sensorless control system and method of permanent magnet synchronous motor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5903128A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>If the magnitude of a voltage command vector to a motor driver is smaller than a preset value in a control period, in each of a predetermined number of subsequent control periods (a compensation period), a pulse voltage vector is added to &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="243"><title>Air bag device and method for folding an air bag</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5957486A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Gas generated from an inflator flows into a first portion of a main bag and each part of an inner bag, and the first portion is inflated toward an area in front of passenger's seat. Then, the gas filling the first portion which has been &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="244"><title>Semiconductor type yaw rate sensor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6028332A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor type yaw rate sensor has a substrate, a beam structure formed from a semiconductor material and having at least one anchor portion disposed on the substrate, a weighted portion located above the substrate a predetermined &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="245"><title>Heat exchanger having several exchanging portions</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5992514A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A first cooling fin and a second cooing fin are separated to have a predetermine clearance, and a plurality of connecting portions for partly connecting the first and second cooling fins are formed. When the first and second cooling fins &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="246"><title>Rotary electric machine and method of manufacturing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6346758B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a rotary electric machine such as a vehicle AC generator, each slot of a stator core has chamfered corners extending over a distance longer than thickness of the core sheet and burrs extending from the core sheet in one direction so &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="247"><title>Vapor compression type refrigerating system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6044655A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A refrigerating system, using CO 2 as a refrigerant, for an air conditioner for an automobile. A pressure at the outlet of the heat emitter 2 is controlled to a target value in accordance with the temperature of the refrigerant at the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="248"><title>Air conditioner with control of compressor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6955060B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In an air conditioner, a target compressor rotation speed is determined based on a target air temperature, which represents an air conditioning load, when an electric compressor is started from a stop state. Thus, an evaporator air &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="249"><title>Apparatus for automatically adjusting aiming of headlights of an automotive &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5877680A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A pitch angle in the back-and-forth direction of the vehicle body is calculated based on output signals of height sensors disposed at front and rear wheels of the vehicle. A vehicle traveling speed is obtained. A vehicle acceleration is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="250"><title>Liquid crystal cell having filling passage preventing turn-around flow of &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5946070A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A first electrode plate and a second electrode plate are overlapped on each other with a seal member and spacer walls interposed therebetween. The cell gap formed between both plates is filled with liquid crystal such as smectic liquid &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="251"><title>Angular velocity sensor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6308567B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A compact angular velocity sensor, which can improve an S/N (signal/noise) ratio. An angular velocity sensor includes an SOI substrate, four oscillatory masses movably supported to the SOI substrate, and four detection electrodes provided &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="252"><title>Engine control signal processing system with frequency analysis by fourier &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6246952B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Only predetermined frequency components included in an ion current flowing between an ignition plug and the ground are extracted from the ion current by means of a low pass filter and a high pass filter as a knock detection signal, that &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="253"><title>Air conditioning apparatus</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6308770B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>According to the present invention, an air conditioning apparatus include a case partitioned into a first air passage and a second air passage by partition plates ( 16-19 ), a heat exchanger such as a heater core. The heater exchanger is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="254"><title>Method for manufacturing semiconductor dynamic quantity sensor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6287885B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a method for manufacturing a semiconductor acceleration sensor, a movable portion including a mass portion and movable electrodes is formed in a single crystal silicon thin film provided on a silicon wafer through an insulation film by &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="255"><title>Mobile robot, automated production system, and mobile robot system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6463360B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A mobile robot placed on an automatic production line is provided. The mobile robot collects information on operating conditions of other mobile robots placed around it and flow of workpieces on the production line and determines action &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="256"><title>Engine control apparatus</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6702718B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An engine control apparatus includes a brake depression degree detecting device for detecting a degree of depression of a brake pedal in a vehicle. A brake depression degree judging device operates for judging whether or not the detected &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="257"><title>Vehicle communication system and method for vehicles capable of automatic &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6195602B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A plurality of electronic control units such as engine ECU, navigation ECU and meter ECU as well as a transponder unit is provided in a vehicle so that those control units communicate with each other through a communication line. Each &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="258"><title>Spark plug for internal combustion engine and method for manufacturing same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6346766B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a spark plug, a chip or a plurality of chips made of Ir alloy are bonded by resistance welding through a stress releasing layer on the respective chip mounting portions of the center and ground electrodes made of Ni base alloy. At the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="259"><title>Emission control system with catalyst warm-up speeding control</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6898927B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An emission control system has a catalyst and a sensor responding to a component of exhaust gas. In order to speed warming up the catalyst, the emission control system increases the amount of heat dissipated by exhaust gas. A diagnosis of &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="260"><title>Fuel injector</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6578775B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a fuel injector, a valve member in a hollow cylindrical shape having a bottom is enclosed and supported in a magnetic cylinder defining a fuel passage to reciprocate in an axial direction. At least two of the ceramic heaters having an &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="261"><title>Apparatus and method for automatically starting and stopping a vehicle engine &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6135920A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An engine automatic speed control apparatus which exhibits a smooth transition from brake release to an engine drive state. An ECU determines braking force such that a vehicle does not move in correspondence with the slope of a road &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="262"><title>Rotating electric machine</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6853112B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A rotating electric machine for a vehicle includes magnet holders for holding permanent magnets. The magnet holder is fitted between adjacent two claw-like magnetic poles of pole cores, and plural permanent magnets are provided to be &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="263"><title>Structure for mounting electronic components and method for mounting the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5898218A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor sensor chip such as an acceleration sensor chip and other electronic components such as controlling semiconductor chips are mounted on and connected to conductor patterns formed on a ceramic package. The ceramic package is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="264"><title>Electrically-driven position changing apparatus</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6230576B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A single actuator such as an electric motor is used to actuate a shift range changing mechanism of an automatic transmission. The motor has a plurality of torque generating units each of which is capable of generating a torque sufficient &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="265"><title>Fuel injection device having heater</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6561168B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A nozzle needle has a hollow tubular form having a closed base end. A heat transfer tube is press fitted into a first magnetic portion. The heat transfer tube surrounds an outer peripheral surface of the nozzle needle. A ceramic heater is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="266"><title>Resin shield circuit device</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6390854B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In the resin shield circuit device, a resin case is provided with a recess having an opening. Each end of connector terminals is exposed out of the resin case and the other end thereof is embedded into the resin case. Base portions of &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="267"><title>Core unit of heat exchanger having electric heater</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6178292B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A core unit of a heat exchanger is composed of a plurality of parallel flat tubes, a plurality of corrugated fins, a support member disposed between two of the corrugated fins and an electric heater disposed inside the support member. The &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="268"><title>Fulcrum blow off valve for use in a shock absorber</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6371264B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A shock absorber includes a rebound valve assembly which performs the flexing disc function normally required for allowing the passage of fluid from one side of a piston assembly to the opposite side during the stroke of the shock &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="269"><title>Surge preventing circuit for an insulated gate type transistor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6385028B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A first Zener diode group, connected between drain and gate terminals of a power MOSFET, causes breakdown in response to a surge voltage applied to the drain terminal. A resistor, provided between the gate terminal of the power MOSFET and &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="270"><title>Tire air pressure monitoring system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6885293B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Provided is a tire air pressure monitoring system capable of grasping the tire positions where there are sensor units even in the case of tire rotation. In the tire air pressure monitoring system, a trigger signal is transmitted from a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="271"><title>Semiconductor device produced by dicing</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6429506B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A protective sheet is fixed to a jig, and regions of the protective sheet corresponding to regions where dicing-cut is to be performed are removed to form grooves. Then, a semiconductor wafer is bonded to the protective sheet at an &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="272"><title>Air conditioner for a vehicle having infrared ray sensor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6202934B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An air conditioner for a vehicle which accurately estimates a thermal load to enhance inside temperature controllability. The air conditioner comprises a first surface temperature sensor for detecting a temperature of an internal surface &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="273"><title>Integrated vehicle control system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6553297B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a vehicular control system, when in the engine ECU, ATECU or brake ECU there occurs important information which requires an urgent response by any of the other ECUs, the important information is transmitted directly to the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="274"><title>Stator core of vehicle rotary electric machine and method of manufacturing the &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6559572B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>Each tooth of a stator core has circumferential projections at an inner tooth edge and circumferential notches at a base portion adjacent to a core back. A width of the teeth at the base portion is larger than a width of the same at the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="275"><title>Gas sensor for vehicle engine having a double-pipe cover</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6279376B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A gas sensor has a housing, a gas sensing element held by the housing and having a gas contact portion and an element cover for covering the gas contact portion. The element cover has a double pipe structure formed by layering an outer &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="276"><title>Fluid injection nozzle</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6405946B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A fuel injector has a chamber between a valve body and a plate in which a plurality of through holes are formed. The chamber has a diameter larger than that of an opening of the valve body. The through holes are opened at an outer chamber &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="277"><title>Electric load drive apparatus</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6545513B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A current control circuit controls a gate potential of a transistor to equalize a load current IL with a trapezoidal wave signal Sb. The trapezoidal wave signal Sb increases at a constant gradient when a drive command signal Sa turns into &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="278"><title>Method for manufacturing semiconductor device having element isolation &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6524890B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>When a semiconductor device having an element isolation structure is formed, first, a trench is formed in a wafer from a principal surface of the wafer, and the trench is filled with an insulating film. Then, the back surface of the wafer &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="279"><title>Method for accurately detecting sensor element resistance</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6084418A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An air-fuel ratio sensor generates linear air-fuel ratio detection signals proportional to concentration of oxygen in exhaust gas from an engine in response to a command voltage from a microprocessor. A bias command signal generated by &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="280"><title>Temperature sensor</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6639505B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A temperature sensor which features improved response characteristics and in which a thermistor element is contained in a metal enclosure in a state where a pair of electrode wires for taking out signals are connected in an exposed manner &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="281"><title>Vehicular brake system</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US5967628A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>When a vacuum booster fails, an pressure amplifying mechanism increases a wheel brake pressure. After that, even when it is detected that the vehicle is brought into a stopped state, the state in which an increased brake fluid pressure is &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="282"><title>Spark plug for apparatus for detecting ion current without generating spike- &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6111345A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>In a spark plug having a generally cylindrically shaped metallic body, a generally cylindrically shaped insulator held in the metallic body, a center electrode held in the insulator, and a ground electrode facing the center electrode, the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="283"><title>Semiconductor dynamic quantity sensor for detecting dynamic quantity in two &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6591678B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A dynamic quantity sensor includes a semiconductor substrate, a movable electrode, first fixed electrodes and second fixed electrodes. The movable electrode includes a mass portion and electrode portions. The mass portion includes two rod &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="284"><title>Multilayer-type piezoelectric actuator</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6522052B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A multilayer-type piezoelectric actuator having a multilayer piezoelectric unit which is capable of enduring the extension of contraction thereof to prevent the disconnection of external electrodes. The multilayer piezoelectric unit ( 2 ) &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="285"><title>Heat exchanger</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6216776B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A heat exchanger has plural flat tubes through which refrigerant flows, and a pair of header tanks disposed on each longitudinal ends of the flat tubes. Each of the flat tubes has a flow passage portion having plural flow passages through &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="286"><title>Heating heat exchanger with electric heat emitter</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6055360A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An electric heat emitter is disposed at a predetermined position in a heat exchanging core portion having a plurality of tubes and corrugated fins. The electric heat emitter includes a positive electrode plate and a negative electrode &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="287"><title>Video telephone device having automatic sound level setting along with &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6281925B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A cellular video telephone terminal is capable of switching its operation mode between a voice communication and a voice and image communication in response to a manual operation on a key. A control unit checks whether the key is operated &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="288"><title>Cellular phone for radio communication system having automatic data conversion &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6600919B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A cellular phone is programmed to convert language and currency of a home country into corresponding language and currency of another country. When the cellular phone is used in the country in which the same communication protocol as that &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="289"><title>Exhaust gas purification system having particulate filter</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6735941B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An engine control unit of an exhaust gas purification system of an internal combustion engine measures a pressure difference between an upstream and a downstream of a diesel particulate filter (DPF) after heating the DPF at least to a &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="290"><title>Method and apparatus for detecting road circumstances around a traveling &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6198426B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>The present position of a previously recognized stationary object group (SOp) is estimated based on past position data and the movement of the traveling vehicle during a past time (&#916;T). A clearance (Mwr, Mwl) between a traveling vehicle ( &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="291"><title>Semiconductor physical quantity sensor and method of manufacturing the same</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6388300B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A semiconductor physical quantity sensor, in which a beam-structure having a movable electrode and a fixed electrode confronted with the movable electrode are integrally formed in one substrate, having a new electric isolation structure.</snippet></document><document id="292"><title>Wireless communication system, fixed base station and mobile terminal station</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6909893B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A radio communication system between a mobile terminal station of a vehicle and a plurality of roadside fixed base stations is so constructed that communication areas of the base stations do not overlap with each other and satisfy the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="293"><title>Vehicle front end structure</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6364403B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A vehicle front end member including at least a radiator has an upper protrusion fixed to an upper insertion hole of a vehicle front end panel, and a lower protrusion fixed to a lower insertion hole of the front end panel. When an &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="294"><title>Cruise control apparatus performing automatic adjustment of object recognition &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6941216B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A cruise control apparatus can control a host vehicle to run with a fixed separation from a preceding vehicle when such a preceding vehicle is detected based on received radar signals and to run at a preset fixed speed when no preceding &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="295"><title>Exhaust gas cleaning device for internal combustion engine</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6829889B2/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>The recycling timing schedule for a diesel particulate filter (DPF) can be easily and accurately determined. There is a differential pressure sensor that detects differential pressure &#916;P in the DPF, and an airflow meter that detects the &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="296"><title>Automatic toll charging system and a vehicle-mounted unit used in the automatic &#8230;</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6019285A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>An automatic toll charging system communicates by radio between roadside units disposed on each gate of a toll road and a vehicle-mounted unit mounted in a vehicle, and automatically charges a toll in a range from an entrance gate to an &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="297"><title>Heat exchanger having multi-hole structured tube</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6340055B1/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>A tube for a heat exchanger has notch portions at a longitudinal direction end portion to be inserted into a header tank. Further, several passage holes are provided in the tube to extend in a longitudinal direction of the tube in which &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="298"><title>Cooling device boiling and condensing refrigerant</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6026891A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>The cooling device of the present invention includes a casing divided into a first fluid passage and a second fluid passage by a fluid separation plate; a heat exchanger disposed to pass through the fluid separation plate, for receiving &#8230;</snippet></document><document id="299"><title>Vehicle communication system for toll collection</title><url>https://patents.google.com/patent/US6081718A/en?assignee=Denso+Corporation&amp;page=2&amp;num=100</url><snippet>To perform communication speedily and reliably at an increased frequency of communication occurrence when providing multiple antenna units which are set to the same frequency, each of antenna units having a gantry in a tollgate is set &#8230;</snippet></document></searchresult>